there is also a friend who is also fighting with one leg, they
есть и друг который с одной ногой тоже
sent him back as if he was fighting with one
воюет обратно отправили как с одной
leg, so they put in a prosthesis
ногой воюет вот так вот протез поставили
and now he has an arm in
и дальше у него сейчас то есть рука в
two places, it is broken
двух местах перелом она не заживает вот
and it is not healing, so he is still being treated and he will recover,
и он лечится до сих пор и он вылечится
everything will grow together, his arm is rotting,
всё она срастётся у него рука гниёт
just stupidly speaking, he will be without an arm, no
просто тупо говоря он будет без руки ну
matter how it sounds, here But he will 100%
как бы это не звучало Вот Но его 100%
be sent because there are no armless or legless people there
отправят потому что там и безруких и без
at all, it
ногих вообще всё равно То есть
turns out that now he does not need to be treated,
получается ему сейчас нужно не лечиться
but to delay the treatment Yes, so that he does not Yes,
а затягивать лечение Да чтобы его не Да
he He is doing just that,
он Он как раз это и
girls, don't switch over, let's have a
делает девчонки не переключайтесь
normal conversation, let's have a normal
нормально пообщаемся нормально
conversation, you will not put us anywhere No,
пообщаемся вы нас никуда не выложите Нет
no, I just want to have a normal conversation with
нет я просто хочу нормально поговорить с
someone because everyone here is shouting and suffering, you are at
кем-то бо тут все кричат маются вы на
Zelensky It seems that everyone tells me that Yes,
Зеленского Похоже мне все так говорят Да
I'm just from Brussels, this is the European Union
я просто я сам из Брюсселя это Евросоюз
Yes, I hung my phage on the back, so I can see how he
Да я повесил фаг сзади свой так я вижу
reacts Where are you from We are from Russia Well, I
реагирует Вы откуда Мы из России Ну я
understood what city Moscow is And where did
понял город какой Москва А откуда
you come to Moscow from, and we ourselves are from,
приехали в Москву а мы сами родом вообще
in principle, from  Domodedovo Podmoskovie
в принципе из Домодедова Подмосковье
I understood and the guy is still standing there I see
понял а Парниша ещё там стоит смотрю
such
такой
a pumped up A well come on Oh yeah good
накаченный А ну давайте О да хорошие
girls you have a clear
девчонки у тебя чёткие
mind What are you talking about here babes Yes just about life there well everything else except war and so on and so forth I mean and so on I was just thinking about it and so on and talk I don't want to talk about it for me there is no bad nation
разговаривать для меня нет плохой нации
there are bad
есть плохие
people not me look I'm just a simple
люди не я смотри я как раз я простой
person I'm interested in talking to
человек мне интересно пообщаться с
ordinary people because these politicians
простыми людьми потому что эти политики
from TV can tell us one thing yes
нам из телевизора одно могут говорить да
Whatever your thoughts I don't quarrel
Какие бы у вас были мысли я не ссорюсь
I'm just wondering how for
мне проу разли просто интересно как
example do people in Russia
например у вас люди в России например
perceive for example why this war
воспринимает из-за чего эта война
started What do you think Well
началась Как вы считаете Ну
president here it started this in
президент вот она и началась это по
fact these are docking
факту это состыковки
Although here the people are not at all at the World Cup in fact
Хотя тут народ вообще ни при ЧМ по факту
and Well it's the presidents who suffer
и Ну это президенты и страдают
because of the throwing and ordinary people suffer because of this well
изза накидали и страдают из-за этого
in fact Yes but I heard for
обычные люди ну по факту Да но я слышал
example that ordinary people from Russia go
например что обычные люди из России идут
sign a contract to fight in
подписывают контракт чтобы воевать в
Ukraine Well there are such people there are I agree
Украине Ну есть такие люди есть согласна
I don't deny  there are people who
Я не отрицаю есть такие люди которые
sign a contract not to
подписывают контракт не из-за того чтобы
kill Ukrainians and so on but for the sake of
убивать украинцев и так далее а ради
money money
денег деньги
another situation is that there are some
ещё ситуация такая то что есть некоторые
who do not have Russian citizenship and
у которых нет гражданства российского и
they go because of citizenship also to
они идут из-за гражданства ещё вот чтобы
get citizenship because there they
получить гражданство потому что там
sign right away they do everything right away Well
сразу подписывают сразу всё делают Ну
here I am what come here It's
вот я что тако иди сюда
cool that's why we kind of you know
Прикольно вот поэтому мы как бы знаешь
when
когда
we kind of like this well you don't want to
мы как бы это как бы ну не хотите да
because we are ordinary people why is it
потому что мы же простые люди зачем
better and by the way and by the way are there any
лучше а кста а кстати а есть какие-то
acquaintances who died in the war I have an
знакомые которые погибли на войне у меня
ex but he didn't die he lost an eye and
бывший но он не погиб он потерял глаз и
that's what
вот а что
happened Well you know probably What is
случилось Ну знаешь наверно Что такое
Bab
баб
Yaga The drone is so big
Яга Дрон такой большой
in short that's it he shot down one And the second one
короче вот то есть один он сбил А второй
caught up with him and that's when wow That is
его догнал и то есть когда ого То есть
he shoots what are they called
он стреляет как это называется
cassettes and that's it flew right into His
кассетами и вот и Ему прилетело прямо
eye that is well his eye remained in
глаз то есть ну глаз у него остался на
place it turns out and that's well he doesn't
месте получается а то есть ну он не
see That is they cleaned everything out they took out
видит То есть ему прочистили всё достали
the fragments but in general they should have Like the drone
осколки вот а вообще должны Как бы Дрон
should have roughly
должен был грубо
speaking his My ex but it turned out
говоря его Моего бывшего а получилось
that instead of my ex
так то что Вместо моего бывшего попал
his bait got in And my ex just lost an
его живец А мой бывший просто потерял
eye and  that is, it turns out Serve died And the
глаз а то есть получается Служи помер А
ex is just without an eye yes yes
у бывшего просто без глаза да да
Cool and it turns out Listen and how did it
Прикольно а получается Слушай а как это
happen like he is fighting now or is he already
вышло типа он сейчас воюет или он уже
home without an eye no He is now in Belgorod he has a
дома без гла нет Он сейчас в Белгороде у
vacation from tomorrow and you are from
него с завтрашнего дня отпуск а вы из
Belgorod No, I mean vacation so if
Белгорода Нет в смысле отпуск так если
he is without an eye He is still fighting he did not
он без глаза Он до сих пор воюет он не
fight he first lay in
воевал он сначала 2 месяца лежал у
Moscow in a
Москве в
hospital for 2 months then they sent him to Belgorod
госпитале потом его отправили в Белгород
to his unit to Sign documents for
в его часть чтобы Подписать документы на
vacation and so on And so yesterday oh it
отпуск и так далее И вот и вчера ой
turns out today at 7:00 in the evening they
получается сегодня ему в 700 вечера его
signed it for him that is vacation so he
подписали то есть отпуск вот он на 2
goes on vacation for 2 months and then they should
месяца едет в отпуск а потом его должны
discharge him How is it correctly said
комиссовать Как правильно это говорится
Well, you understand Well, I understand yes, exclude from the
Ну вы поняли Ну я понял да исключить из
army or how it is with those soldiers Yes but
армии или как это у тех армейцев Да но
rarely excludes I have another
редко исключает У меня есть ещё один
acquaintance my sister's friend he also lost
знакомый у сестры друг он тоже потерял
an eye but he was not well there was no this
глаз но его не вот ну не было этой
Commissar That is, he is also on vacation
Комиссар То есть он также в отпусках
also goes back [ __ ] that is without an
также обратно идёт выеба то есть без
eye and sends
глаза и отправляет
him there is a friend who with one leg also
его есть друг который с одной ногой тоже
fights back sent back as with one
воюет обратно отправили как с одной
he fights with his leg, that's how they put in a prosthesis
ногой воюет вот так вот протез поставили
and then who's a foreign city Excuse the
и дальше кого чужой город Извини за
expression, but is he a contract soldier or who is a
выражение а это он контрактник или кто
contract soldier Yes, how is it on the Protest and
контрактник Да как как это на проте и
what is he doing there in the wo I thought it was I
что он делает там на воне Я думал это я
saw these videos that On crutches they
видел эти ролики что На костылях типа
send them to fight, but I thought it was
отправляют воевать но я думал это фейки
Ukrainian fakes No No There are, but it depends on
украинские нет Нет Есть но смотря в
what unit you find there are Where are there
какой части ты находишь есть Где
adequate understanding people and there are where it's
адекватные понимающие люди а есть где
just you know,
просто вот знаешь
just like
просто как бы
money in money
деньги в деньгах
IT and it also
ИТ ещ
turns out like he says that he is
получается как он говорит ти что его
being sent with a prosthesis to fight again what does
отправляют с протезом воевать снова что
he say to this
он на это
because at first the
говорит потому что это момен сначала
girl accepted the Armed Forces without a leg, as it
девушка приняла без ноги ВС как бы как
should be, that is, normally, but when she
положено то есть нормально но когда она
found out that he was not
узнала то что его не
for me I say so out of worry
ко меня Я говорит так на переживаниях
We went through all this together so that he
Вот это всё мы вместе проходили чтобы он
could learn to stand, it turns out, everything else
учился стоять получается всё прочее
says, and then back after
говорит а тут обратно после вот этого
all this, in all these moments, they send him
всего всех моментах его отправляют
back, this is already inadequate, that is, there
обратно это уже неадекватно то есть там
were trials and so on, roughly
и суды были и так далее всем грубо
speaking, again, money rules for expression
говоря опять же за выражение правят
So what about the parents What do the
деньги Так а что родители Что
relatives say to all this,
родственники говорят на это всё ничего
they don't say anything  also because of the expression
они так же из за выражение
again Well it's awful how is it that a man without a
опять Ну это ужас как это человека без
leg on the protest is again forced to fight brutally
ноги на проте снова воевать насильно
Well I'm saying again it depends on the
жесть Ну я же говорю опять же зависит от
unit I have a friend who
части вот у меня есть знакомый который
just had one wound pelvic it turns
просто у него было одно ранение тазовые
out he had a pelvic wound just
получается его с тазовым ранением просто
once Komi Sirova
разу Коми сирова
everything
всё
yes that is it depends on the unit Who
да то есть там зависит от частей Кто как
treats people how someone fights for money
относится к людям кто-то за деньги воюет
And someone well mobilizes someone and it
А кто-то ну кого-то мобилизует а
turns out that is you already have three
получается то есть у тебя это уже трое
wounded friends Yes it turns out Well yes and
раненых знакомых Да выходит Ну да а
there are dead there are no dead missing
погибшие есть погибших нету пропавшие
in action No also no yes I understand
безвести Нету тоже нету да понял отец у
my father was killed but he died
меня погибший был но он у меня погибший
in Chechnya in the war and Well that was a
в Чечне на войне а Ну это ещё
long time ago
давно-давно
yes And your boyfriend doesn't want to go to
да А парень у тебя не хочет идти на
war no can you say Let's turn the
войну нет можеш сказать Пусть тише
music down because I feel bad for you
музыку сделать потому что я вас плохо
Listen
Слыш из
guys will make music out of music so note
музыки ребята сделат музыку так ноте
super you know Here everyone is shouting Drunk
супер знаете Тут все такие кричат Пьяные
there swearing at each other We are also drunk
там матюкаются друг на Мы тоже выпившие
but we have respect not you are normal Yes
но мы имеем уважение не вы нормальные Да
I just like to talk
я как раз вот я люблю поговорить просто
to real people who like that  they
с настоящими людьми которые вот
communicate in a cultured way, it's cool
культурно общаются это классно Потому
Because now in this world, you know, there is a lack of
что сейчас в этом мире знаете не хватает
spiritual human communication
именно душевного человеческого общения
Yes, roughly speaking, now even the War
Да вот грубо говоря сейчас даже Война
is going on because of a simple misunderstanding, and it's
идёт за недопонимание просто а страдают
just people who suffer, girls, by the way,
просто люди девушки жё меня кстати
my name is Andrey, what is my name? Yulia
Андрей зовут вас как меня зовут Юля
Alena Yulia Alena Alena, do you have
Алёна Юлия Алёна Алёна а у вас есть
any acquaintances who were killed or wounded?
какие-то знакомые погибшие или раненые
No. I just have a Mom who lives with
нет У меня только вот Мама живёт с
a man, he was in the war, so he came back
мужчиной он был на войне вот он приехал
because of his wounds, something happened to his arm
из из-за ранений у него с рукой что-то
There were two
Там было два
re-injuries Yes, and fragments and fractures in two
переро Да и осколки и переломы в двух
places on his arm That is, he now goes
местах руки Вот он то есть сейчас ездит
to Moscow, so that
в Москву вот чтобы там
everything is there And how much did they pay him for this
всё А сколько ему выплатили за это
arm, about D or 3
руку около Д или 3
million, and what did they buy with this money, what
млн и что они купили на эти деньги что
can you buy there with this money, I don't
можно купить там на эти деньги я не
understand, it's not enough Well, in short, in general,
понимаю это же мало Ну короче в общем
they paid him about 12 million for all the wounds,
ему выплатили за все ранения около 12
yes, well, I heard that they pay 7 million for a death
млн вот да ну я слышал что за смерть 7
Well, 12 million for a
млн платят Ну 12 млн за
wound, for each wound, even if Dahl
ранение за каждое ранение если даже Даля
3 ml for each wound
3 мл за каждое ранение
I mean, that is, if he was hit by three bullets,
В смысле то есть если ему три пули
it's 9 million  Well, roughly speaking, yes,
попало это 9 млн Не ну грубо говоря да
that is, for each
то есть за каждое
wound if there were a lot of bullets at once. That is
ранение если зараз дев пуль Вот то это
one wound. And if, for example, one
одно ранение А если Например одно
wound, roughly speaking, there are cartridges there in the
ранение там грубо говоря касетоны там в
leg there, roughly speaking, like this, that
ногу там вотт грубо говоря вот так вот
is, it is considered one wound.
то есть это считается как одно ранение
That is, 3 million are paid for it.
То есть за него выплачивается 3 млн
Then if after you, Kato, the moments like
потом если после тебя Като моменты как
this, that is, they treated and cured him, and he
это всё то есть обработали вылечили е он
went back again, roughly speaking, they
обратно поехал ещ раз его грубо говоря
shot him there, dro. That is, that is another 3
там выстрелили дро Вот то есть это ещё 3
million. That is, for each
млн То есть за каждое вот такое вот
wound like this. Wait, if 12 million. That she was
ранение Подожди если 12 млн Это её
wounded four different times. That is, he somehow had a
четыре раза ранили разных это как-то у
concussion and, in short, in the kidney
него и контузия была и короче в почку
there were wounds or in the liver, then in the leg,
там ранения или в печень потом в ногу
then a broken arm in two places. All
потом перелом руки в двух места это всё
this happened at different times. Yes,
это всё в разны в разное время было да
yes, yes, yes, that is, he is the Terminator. And how did
да дада да вот это он Терминатор А как
he fight like that, wounded again, I dont know. He
он так воевал раненый снова я не знаю он
was in hospitals, then he was back, and
лежал в госпиталях потом его обратно и
literally. Well, 3 months ago, he was
вот буквально Ну 3 месяца назад его
only sent on vacation. Well, thats just it.
только отпустили в отпуск ну вот просто
If I first thought, Well, how is it that
это если его я сначала Думаю Ну как это
he was wounded four times,
это четыре раза его ранили
to be treated. Well,  he is also in shock
полечить Ну он тоже в шоке
but there is just such a feeling that you know the
но просто есть такое ощущение что знаешь
only way out is to die in
единственный выход - это сдохнуть по
fact that is what he has now that is his
факту так и есть у него сейчас то есть
arm is broken in two places it does not
рука в двух местах перелом она не
heal so he is still being treated and
заживает вот и он лечится до сих пор и
he will recover everything will grow together his
он вылечится всё она срастётся у него
arm is rotting just stupidly speaking he will be
рука гниёт просто тупо говоря он будет
without an arm well as it may sound here But
без руки ну как бы это не звучало Вот Но
he will 100% be sent because there are
его 100% отправят потому что там и
armless and legless people there anyway that
безруких и без ногих вообще всё равно То
is I bring a friend prime that is it turns out
есть я дру приме приводи То есть
he does not need treatment now
получается ему сейчас нужно не лечиться
atya that is
атя
exactly what he is doing he should
он как раз это и делает его должны
Kosovo in general in fact that is he
Косова вообще по сути а то есть он
deliberately treats his arm poorly like so that
специально плохо лечит руку типа чтобы
it is more like yes yes it is he walks Oh
она больше гла типа да да она он ходит О
he pays the hospital that is the hospital so that
он платит больнице то есть госпиталю
they extend it
чтобы ему продлили вот это вот
all this is brutal no Yes I understand that is it
всё жесть нет Да я понял то есть и
turns out They deliberately treat it poorly
получается Они специально плохо лечат
like so that it
типа чтобы она дольше
takes longer to heal he does not treat it at all he just
заживала он вообще её не лечит он просто
pays money and that's it go there Well it is just
платит деньги и всё ехать туда Ну просто
not clear what people are fighting for that is really
непонятно за что воюют люди вот реально
why your guys are dying young that
что ваши погибают пацаны молодые что
ours for
наши за
what is it just  A clash between two
что это вот просто Столкновение двух
presidents and simply because of some
президентов и просто из-за вот какой-то
people die there and 18 years old and 19 years old you
люди погибают там и 18 лет и 19 у вас
generally I am silent that is children Well that is
вообще я молчу то есть детей Ну то есть
well in general how much 16 years old as they wrote
ну вообще насколько 16 лет как писали
take Well I don't know the truth you don't know the
берут Ну я не знаю правда ты не знаю
truth I don't know No in fact that's
правды не знаю Нет на самом деле вот
just what they said they wrote well well they
просто так говорили писали вот
also take us from the army we are
ну нас тоже с армии забирают нас у нас в
forced to sign a contract in the army
армии заставляют подписать договор
in short I have a
на у нас короче у меня У
classmate's brother is now getting into the
одногруппницы брат сейчас получается в
army and that's how before there that is they taught
армию и вот как раньше там то есть учили
trained All this in the army Now there is
обучали Вот это всё в армии Сейчас
no such thing that is they don't force
такого нет то есть не заставляют просто
conscripts to just collect the remains of Drones on the
срочников собирать остатки Дронов по
street all iro this is some kind of nonsense I had an
улице всё иро это бред какой-то У меня э
acquaintance he was from Russia Yes a childhood friend
знакомый был он из России Да друг
In short he came to visit his grandmother
Короче он к бабушке приезжал
on about Serve hard to hear a girl
по о Служи плохо слышно бы девушка
speaks she speaks with a friend Yes it
говорит она с другом говорит Да мне
hums loudly to me it turns out that I
сильно гудит во получается что у меня
had an acquaintance Yes a friend childhood sa Let
был знакомый Да друг детство са Пусть
Alena listen too al It's illegal
Алёна тоже послушает ал Это незаконно
that's clear Alena the law Listen I'll
это понятно Алёна закон Послушай я
tell Yes because they said that
расскажу Да потому что говорили что вот
there young guys  they take them without
там молодых парней забирают без
preparation Yes, not only young adults, I
подготовки Да не только молодых взрослых
had a friend too A childhood friend,
тоже у меня был друг Друг детства
he was constantly pressed against his grandmother, he
он к бабушке постоянно прижал он см
was from Rostov, we were constantly
родом из Ростова мы постоянно
writing to each other on VKontakte and Odnoklassniki
списывались ВКонтакте в Одноклассниках
Yes, he Well, it was cool, in short, he
Да он Ну прикольно было короче он
was generally a teacher, a physics teacher Yes And
был вообще учителем учителе физики Да И
so in the twenty-second year in Rostov, he
вот в двадцать втором году в Ростове ему
received a summons, they took him to the front,
пришла повестка его забрали на фронт
you know how long they trained him there, how long for
знаешь сколько его там
me, a week, but days,
тренировали сколько мне неделю но дней
but days Oh, yes, I also know about that, they
но дней А ну да я тоже про такое сы
took him in Rostov, they gathered them for 3 days, they
забрали в Ростове собрали их 3 дня
kept them at the distribution point, they
держали на распределительном пункте
put them on a plane and brought them somewhere to
посадили в самолёт и привезли куда-то в
Donetsk Donetsk, how long did he live after
Донецк Донецк сколько Он прожил после
leaving the airport What do you
выхода с аэропорта Как ты
think, oh, it hung up, developed, there is,
думаешь ой зависла развила есть
there is, no, don't disappear, don't disappear,
есть не не пропадай не пропадай
please Here, everything is here, I also don't
пожалуйста Здесь всё я тоже мы не
switch, if anything, you
переключаем если что
know how many, here they were brought to Donetsk,
знаете скоко вот их привезли в Донецк
how long did he
сколько Он
live Well, about three days, 3 days, 3 days, they
прожил Ну суток трое 3 дня 3 дня они
arrived, they were brought to you have and
приехали их привезли в
maybe you saw, uh, it was
располагаете и может видели ээ было как
just New Year's, they gathered them, they gathered in
раз Новый год их собрали их собрали в
this, in the assembly hall, watch
этом в актовом зале смотреть приветствие
Putin's greeting and an American missile
Путина и прилетел американская ракета
flew in which High Mars blew up this
прилетела которая Хай Марс разнесла это
vocational school in Makeyevka,
ПТУ в Макеев
simply simply in short blew up 300+
просто просто короче разнесла 300 С
something dead there were 300+ something
чем-то погибших было 300 С чем-то
dead and
погибших и
so his mother wrote to me because well
вот мне его мама да писала потому что ну
she knew my mother and said sonny He
она знала мою маму и говорит сыночек
was at war for 3 days he didn't even have time to
Побыл на войне 3 дня он не успел даже
pick up a machine gun you know why he's
автомат в руки взять понимаешь за что он
not guilty of anything at all he didn't
не виноват вообще ни в чём он никого
even kill anyone he didn't shoot even once why did
даже не убил не стрелял ни разу за что
this missile fly at him that for nothing
ракета эта ему прилетела что Ни за что
just like that for nothing right now just a
просто так не за что сейчас прямо
second and they paid Yes they paid
секунду просто и выплатили Да выплатили
7 million and Yes money is nothing
7 млн и Да деньги это нет ничто Челове
For me it's money roughly speaking a
для меня это деньги вот грубо говоря
stupid piece of paper today it's here tomorrow and
тупая бумажка сегодня она есть завтра и
No especially my mother also says yes she says
Нет особено мама тоже говорит да говорит
that his mother says he died and that's it
что его мама говорит вот он умер и всё у
I don't have a child I have se Milne but no
меня нет ребёнка есть се Милн но нет
child and ure Return Yes and a friend of mine uh
ребёнка а уре Верните Да а у знакомой ээ
says he had a son who was wounded twice you
говорит два раза раненый был сын вы Два
Made payments twice but the son was returned the son
раза делали выплаты но сына вернули сын
returned yes that is it turns out
вернулся да то есть получается
uh She received 7 million but there is no son and the
э-э Она получила 7 млн но сына нет а
neighbor received  6 million and there is a son
соседка получила 6 млн и есть сын
wounded but there is yes Well this is what she
раненый но есть да Ну это же и она
says Well like yes It turns out how
говорит Ну типа да Получается как
unfair if he was wounded
несправедливо если бы ранили его
several times yes well but the son returned It's
несколько раз да ну но сын вернулся Это
like Here you rented out a car they drove it
как Вот Машину сдал в аренду на ней
but the car returned
покатались но машина вернулась
and so if you took the car and sold it and that's it
а так если Тачку взял и её продал и всё
there is money but no car Well this is very
деньги есть а Тачки нет Да ну это очень
cruel I don't understand at all why
жестоко я не понимаю вообще для чего
there is a war because roughly speaking before
идёт Война потому что грубо говоря до
this there was also a war like Ukrainians
этого тоже была война как бы и украинцы
Russians they stuck
русские они держались
together grandfathers grandfathers Ours but not everyone was
вместе деды деды Наши да не всё было
together that is to me even distant
вместе то есть мне даже дальние
relatives They that is Ukrainian That is to say
родственники Они то есть Украин Вот то
everyone stuck together But now we are
есть как бы все держались вместе А сечас
fighting we don't understand me at all I do
за воюем мы вобще не понимаем меня вот
n't know what to call him closer he is
го не знаю назвать бличе он
Ukrainian cool Where is he from
украинец прикольно Откуда он родом
Odessa Cool And how long has he lived in Russia my
Одесса Прикольно А как давно в России
parents divorced When I was a
живёт мене родители развелись Когда было
year and a half I moved Well keep in mind
полтора года Я переехал Ну Имей в виду
How many years has it been there already 20 15 I am now
Сколько лет это уже там 20 15 мне сечас
Understand there are people who understand What is behind
Поня есть люди которые понимат Что за
the howling I communicate and there are those who are just
воем общаюсь а есть которые просто
real animals you can't call them anything  they
реально животные их никак не назвать они
immediately start yes we are there Russians Yes we are
сразу начинают да мы там русские Да мы
you there back and forth that is the same thing
вас там туда-сюда то есть то же самое
Ukrainians and that is just Well and what is the point of
украинцы и то есть просто Ну а смысл
arguing in fact before that we all
ругаться по факту до этого мы все вместе
fought together we stuck together for each other
воевали мы держались друг за друга
USSR yes it was a Great Power yes yes yes And
СССР да Великая держава была да да да А
now what are we fighting for we don't know just well
сейчас за что воюем мы не знаем просто
really that's why I don't know
вот ну реально поэтому я не знаю вот
when this engagement starts I
когда начинает вот это вот зацепление я
can yell there well just kind of
могу там там наорать вот ну просто как
rudely express what Well why are you
бы грубо высказать то что Ну для чего ты
saying this and why are you showing off
это говоришь и зачем ты это понтуешься
these they just switch when you
эти вот они просто переключаются когда и
start talking about the facts Well this is
начинаешь говорить по факту Ну это вот в
mainly for those who are under 18 that is they
основном которым нет 18 то есть они
have not seen life they don't know anything that is
жизни не видали они ничего не знают то
these thirty year olds
есть сидят вот эти вот тридцатилетние
fourteen year old who are well-read
четырнадцатилетний которые начитанные
just here are the decrees yes And this is in your
просто вот постановы да А вот это у вас
Domodedovo there is an airport there they didn't
в Домодедова там же аэропорт там его не
bomb it no sweat I looked at what they wrote Yes
бомбили нет пото Я смотрел что писали Да
what was there some kind of plan carpet what is
что там какая-то план ковёр было что
it now I'll explain I have a brother well
это сейчас объясню у меня родной брат ну
I live with him in Domodedovo  Here he
я с ним в Домодедово живу Вот он у меня
works as a merchandiser at my warehouse and in the summer
работает на складе товароведом и летом
It was When a drone flew in but it was
Это было Вот когда прилетел Дрон но его
shot down and the remains of the drone flew into their
сбили и остатки дрона прилетел им на
warehouse I won't say Which warehouse did the
склад не буду говорить на Какой склад
remains fly in that is, well, a
вот прилетело остатки то есть ну
hot beaten drone well, well,
горячего избитого дрона вот ну по склад
of course, the warehouse burned down there, thank God That
конечно же там ну сгорело слава богу То
all this was done on time and people
что это всё сделали вовремя и люди
stayed alive post people people yes people that's
остались живы пост люди люди да люди это
yes because then Here was a kov Well that's
да потому что тогда Вот был ков Ну вот
because I was watching the news Yes, there they are
потому что я смотрел новости Да вот там
bombing Ryazan Anya they are bombing Volgograd there is a
Рязань бомбят Ань бомбят Волгоград там
horror there bomb Yes it is horror there and people are screaming
ужас бом Да там это ужас и люди пищат
They are filming a video and screaming they are scared Well
Они снимают видео и кричат им страшно Ну
yes I am That is exactly it in this
да мне Вот именно вот в этой как бы
moment I just feel sorry for the children okay well
моменте жалко просто детей ладно ну с
I lived with him for 20 years but I lived I
ним я 20 лет прожила но я прожила мне
just feel
просто
sorry That is to say I feel sorry for the children
жалко Вот то есть мне жалко детей
who are under a year old who basically has
которым по ле годе который в принципе
not seen life for what they
жизни не видел за что они вообще это
deserved this for even those very ones who are
заслужили вот Даже те самые которые вот
living those moments that are being bombed right now
живя тех моментов которых прямо вот
really specifically That's what
бомбят вот реально конкретно Вот за что
these children deserved I feel sorry for the children Okay
эти дети заслужили жалко Вот детей Ладно
there  I'll go The drone will fly in I've lived for 20
там вот я пойду Дрон прилетит я уже 20
years already I know what life is
лет прожила Я знаю что такое жизнь то
that you can't help no one will help you
что ты не поможешь тебе никто не поможет
you live for yourself for yourself
ты живёшь сам для себя сам за себя вот
for the children it's really a pity I understood But this is
для детей реально жалко понял А вот это
what is happening there now too Kursk yes it turns out
что сейчас там тоже Курск да получается
Kursk Ukraine took part of the Kursk
Курск же Украина забрала часть Курской
region
области
Russia can't win it back it
Россия никак не может отвоевать
turns out Yes I don't know they
получается Да не знаю вот отвоевали
kind of won it back yes I have friends
вроде как отвоевали да у меня знакомы
Well we met him at the theater roulette
есть Ну ну мы с ним тоже в теат рулетке
We were also sitting with him
познакомились Мы также сидели с ним
talking That is he himself is kind of
разговаривали То есть он сам как бы
Ukrainian too but he is for Russia That is
украинец тоже но он за Россию Вот то
there is also a divorce of parents but he
есть там тоже развод родителей но он
stayed not with his mother but with his father that is there his
остался не с мамой а с папой то есть там
mother was Ukrainian and the father was Russian but
мама украинка была папа Русский вот но
he says that everything seems to be going according to
он говорит то что вроде как всё идёт по
plan But I don't know how according to plan That is no matter
плану А как по плану я не знаю То есть
what he doesn't finish telling them either you
как бы он не договаривал тоже им же
can't say
нельзя говорить
pose no don't hang out don't hang out developed Yeah
пози не не зависаю не зависа развила Ага
that's it I know what I can't
вот получается я вот знаешь что не могу
understand I'm looking at you have these
понять я смотрю вот это у вас есть эти
Chechen Battalions Akhmat Yes they are
чеченские Батальоны Ахмат Да они что-то
constantly filming something  video we are there We are there We are
постоянно снимают видео мы там Мы там Мы
there And I didnt see them
там А я что-то не видел чтобы они
dying or being wounded, yes I
погибали или ранеными были да Мне
think its a
кажется это
setup because they are in the Kursk
постанова потому что они вот в Курской
region, they are the Akhmat battalion
области они ческий батальон Ахмат
Yes, thats it Well, yes, thats a
Да это Ну да это
setup they can just come
постанова они могут вообще приехать
for show, pretend that they
чисто для виду сделать вид то что они
were there, take off and leave, thats all
там были снять и уехать вот всё потому
because I saw When they were showing off in the Kursk region,
что я вил Когда в Курской области
showing off, when the attack began, they
понтовались понтовались как пошла атака
abandoned the conscripts Yes, and they themselves ran away
кинули срочников Да а сами убежали
Yes, they suffer the most, they literally
Да больше всего страдают они буквально 4
live for 4 months during training, then they are sent
месяца учебки живут потом их отправляют
immediately either to Kursk or Belgorod Yes,
сразу либо на Курск либо на Белгород Да
we, yes, the boys, in other words, food, not present,
у нас да пацанам рубо говоря еду не прис
that is, we are gathering, well, we, as
то есть мы собираемся вот ну у нас как
if I myself am from a village, that is, we have
бы я сама родом из деревни То есть у нас
a lot of people when this mobilization, that
много кого когда вот эта мобилизация то
is, began. They took away a lot of
есть началась Вот у нас много забрали
young guys from us, and that is, as if I
молодых пацанов и то есть как бы я
used to be a patriot, I honestly
раньше была патриотка честно
admit. And we collected, that is, food,
признаюсь Вот и Мы собирали то есть
there are pills, that is, all the
продукты там таблетки То есть все
villages, that is, they took it out because
деревни то есть вывозили потому что это
all this is not issued, its really not
всё не выдаётся это реально всё не
issued, that is, they either buy it themselves, yes
выдают то есть они либо сами покупают да
or  here are these parcels, that is, we
либо вот эти вот передачки то есть у нас
have a girl e 27 26 Well, I won't lie,
есть девчонка е 27 26 Ну не буду врать
in short, well, well, roughly speaking, 20, so she
короче ну вот ну грубо говоря 20 вот она
collects all this around the village and with her
это всё собирает по деревне и со своим
husband She takes it and distributes it, that
мужем Она везёт это и распределяет то
is, in parts, food, that is, pills,
есть по частям продукты то есть таблетки
that's all, But nothing
вот так вот всё А ничего не
is given out, so it turns out that instead of
выдаётся так получается вместо того
telling Putin that "Bring the boys
чтобы сказать Путину что Верните пацанов
back," they go and give them
назад они ездят ещё передают им
pills, food, like, yeah, yeah Look, in short,
таблеточки еду типа да да Смотри короче
who went against Pun, for example, the
кто против пуна ступал например тот же
same Navalny You know, then there
самый Навальный Знаешь потом ещё кто-то
was someone else before him, they all got jailed, yeah But
до него был вот их всех посадили да Но
why, why, why, instead of what,
зачем зачем зачем они вместо того что
look, it turns out I don't understand Putin
смотри получается я не понимаю Путин
is robbing Russia But these acquaintances from
грабит Россию А вот эти знакомые из
the village, yes, instead of going about
деревни да вместо того чтобы заниматься
their lives, somehow helping their
своей жизнью как-то помогать своим
relatives She collects food,
родственникам Она собирает продукты
medicine, and takes it to help the military Well,
лекарства и возит военным помогать Ну
yes Well, this is like once in No, in
это да Ну это в как бы в раз в Не ну в
some units it is given out, that is,
некоторых частях это выдаётся то есть
you understand, there is such a situation that there is
понимаешь бывает такая ситуация то что
a shortage not Well, it turns out that she
нехватка не Ну получается что она
supports the war, it turns out, yes she Yes,
поддерживает войну выходит да она Да она
she is a real patriot That is  I'm
она реально патриотка То есть как бы я
also for Putin I'm against Putin I
тоже за Путина Я против Путина Ничего
don't say anything I don't have anything against That's it, that
как бы не говорю не имею против Вот вот
's it, well, everyone is for their own
то есть как бы ну Каждый за своего
president, roughly speaking, that is,
президента по сути грубо говоря то есть
for me, Putin has done nothing bad,
для меня Путин ничего плохого не сделал
that is, as I drank for him That is, I wo
то есть как я это пил за него То есть я
n't say anything bad about him, but what's
буду про него слова я плохого не скажу а
good for you That's how I understand it,
что хорошего для тебя Вот я так понимаю
that you were born under Putin and live under
что ты родилась при Путине и живёшь при
Putin What's good when I lost my
Путине Да что хорошего когда я потеряла
father I had payments everything was
отца у меня были выплаты всё было
on time then stop stop stop stop stop stop you
вовремя то стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп ты
lost your father in the second Chechen
потеряла отца на второй чеченской
campaign Yes, I had payments I
компании Да у меня были выплаты у меня
had benefits and so on That is, I
были пособия и так далее То есть у меня
had everything for free that is, food once
было всё бесплатное то есть еда ещ раз
again Wait Well, this is this it was
ещё раз Подожди Да ну это это это тебе
n't Putin who gave you this, this is the state Yes, from the
дал не Путин это государство Да из
taxes of your mother and your neighbors, yes, it
налогов твоей мамы и твоих соседей да э
made you payments it took your dad away from you
тебе делало выплаты оно забрало у тебя
abandoned him to die in Grozny Now
кинула его умереть в Грозном сейчас
I'll interrupt you, can I have my dad, he didn't go
перебью вас можно папа у меня пошёл не
because he was forced to but he went of his
из-за того то что его застави а пошёл по
own free will That is, he wanted to go himself he
своей воле Вот то есть он сам захотел он
went because his brother also
пошёл потому что у него родной брат тоже
fought there they  somehow What Well they
там воевал они как-то Что Ну они очень
communicated very well Well, they, roughly
хорошо общались вот Ну они короче грубо
speaking, were dependent on each other, like
говоря друг другу были зависимы вот как
they were twins, as they say That's
они были двойняшки как это говорится
right, they couldn't live without communication and it
Правильно они не могли без общения и
turned out that they ended up in the same
получилось так то что они попали в одну
unit and that's what happened Yes Well, it
часть и вот случилось так да Ну
turns out, look, that
получается смотри то
is, the government unleashed a war in Chechnya,
есть власть развязала войну в Чечне так
recruiting people Like your dad, throwing
набирала людей Как твой папа туда кидала
them there like meat, just like meat Well,
их как мясо просто там как мясо Ну
how many guys died, they were just thrown there to
сколько погибло парней просто там на
storm the assaults
штурмы их бросали Да
And do you think it's good that you were
и ты считаешь что хорошо что тебе за это
given money for this, in short, no, money is not the most important thing
короче дали деньги нет деньги не главные
in this life, seriously, no I do
в этой жизни серьёзно нет Я за денег
n't say anything for money
ничего не говорю
Putin gave except payments for
дал Путин кроме выплат за
dad Well, I don't know, thanks to him, I'm
папу Ну не знаю благодаря ему вот я
sitting here drinking beer now, that is,
сейчас сижу пью пиво то есть у меня как
everything is calm with me Everything Stop, stop, stop, one
бы всё спокойно Всё Стоп стоп стоп ещё
more time, how are you, thanks to him, you're
раз ещё раз как ты благодаря ему ты
drinking beer, thanks to the fact that you
пьёшь пиво благодаря тому что ты
earned money and bought beer Well, it's
заработала деньги и Купила пиво Ну это
clear that I'm sitting here, I have
понятное дело то что я вот сижу у меня
no drones or anything That is, everything is guarded by me
ни Дронов ничего То есть у меня всё
That is, now, roughly speaking, a
охраняет То есть сейчас грубо говоря
drone will fly, that is, the yoke will be shot down
Дрон вот полетит то есть иго собьют
immediately That is, for me  nothing just
сразу же то есть для меня ничего как раз
on That's just the opposite look because of
на Вот как раз наоборот смотри из-за
Putin and the war started Well that's true
Путина и началась война Так ну это да
But if it weren't for him it would have been calm he
Но если бы не он было бы спокойно он
made it uneasy Well I don't know
наоборот сделал неспокойно Ну я не знаю
who's to blame in this situation you know I
кто в этой ситуации виноват понимаешь Я
told you that like the president
же тебе говорила то что как бы президент
for everyone is his own president then
для каждого свой президент то для
I'm interested in you If it wasn't
вас мне интересно Если был например не
Putin for example And it was someone else what would
Путин А был бы кто-то другой что хуже
have been worse what he did
было бы что сделал
like that
такого гово
I'm for him that is no women will have to fight
я за него то есть на будет бабам воевать
I'll go fight for Putin that is the most
я пойду за Путина воевать то есть самое
that the black woman understood that it smells like
что чёрная поняла что пахнет
fried That's
жареным Вот это
just [ __ ] hell in short
капец просто короче
everything was here
тут всё было
and counting money yes for the dead for the
и считание денег да за погибших за
wounded and such an attitude Well as a
раненых и такое отношение Ну в
result of everything they said
результате всего что они рассказывали
she is for Putin she is because it is he I was
она за Путина она потому что это он я
born under
родилась при
Putin How can you say after all this
Путине Как как можно после всего этого
that you support
говорить что ты поддерживаешь
the black woman it's still normal Yes she understood she
чёрненькая ещё нармально Да она понимала
says that who is against You know that it's
говорит что кто против Вы знаете что
impossible yes it's just
нельзя да это просто
this is very indicative Video let's make a
это очень показательное Видео давайте
lacquer squeak comment and send it to all we know
лак писка комент и скиньте его всм знам
Glory to
Слава
Ukraine letter on y instag I don't know for
Украине пись на й instag Я не знаю для
this is why you should look at the office
це то для чого тоб там дивитись на офес
and for you one two or three clicks and you
а для тебе один два або три клика а ты
try me and I will be like in me there are
тримае мене и я буду каза в мене там
a bunch of fouls and in me there will be a cool mood
Купа фолов и в мене буде класний настр
to make new cool video Write to my
робити нове крут видео Пиши на мий
Instagram Popik Andriy Oh
Instagram Попик Андрий О
so come on I'm
так давай я тебя
waiting for you N
чекаю N